[
    {
        "question_text":"This is a demo question",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"First Answer",
            "answer_2":"Second Answer",
            "answer_3":"Third Answer",
            "answer_4":"Fourth Answer",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"What is Isaac's middle name? ",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Edward",
            "answer_2":"Edmund",
            "answer_3":"Troy",
            "answer_4":"Trey",
            "right_answer":2
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Which American President appears on the $10 bill? ",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Abraham Lincoln",
            "answer_2":"George Washington",
            "answer_3":"Andrew Jackson",
            "answer_4":"Alexander Hamilton",
            "right_answer":4
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"Where would you fin a landform called a cay?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Desert",
            "answer_2":"Mountain",
            "answer_3":"Ocean",
            "answer_4":"Tundra",
            "right_answer":3
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"What is the name of the blogger narrated by Kristen Bell in this eponymous TV show?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Elle Woods",
            "answer_2":"Miss Secret",
            "answer_3":"Gossip Girl",
            "answer_4":"Carrie",
            "right_answer":3
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"In what game can you be skewered, forked, or pinned by your opponent?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Chess",
            "answer_2":"Checkers",
            "answer_3":"Fencing",
            "answer_4":"Curling",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"What is the garment that helps Harry Potter move around Hogwarts unseen?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"A Jacket",
            "answer_2":"A Blanket",
            "answer_3":"A Sweater",
            "answer_4":"A Cloak",
            "right_answer":4
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"What kind of bird is Blue from the movie Rio?",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"Macaw",
            "answer_2":"Toucan",
            "answer_3":"Hummingbird",
            "answer_4":"Blue Jay",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"",
            "answer_2":"",
            "answer_3":"",
            "answer_4":"",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"",
            "answer_2":"",
            "answer_3":"",
            "answer_4":"",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"",
            "answer_2":"",
            "answer_3":"",
            "answer_4":"",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    },
    {
        "question_text":"",
        "answers":{
            "answer_1":"",
            "answer_2":"",
            "answer_3":"",
            "answer_4":"",
            "right_answer":1
        }
    }
]